♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 27=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 27 =
Thin.
رفيع.
Sihan?
سيهان؟
Why are you back?
لماذا عدت
You are on your own now, Mr. Fu.
أنت وحدك الآن ، السيد فو.
Go for it.
أذهب خلفها.
I don't think Mr. Fu knows this,
لا أعتقد أن السيد فو يعرف هذا ،
but Yun Xiangxiang always likes her hotpot spicy.
لكن يون شيانغشيانغ تحب دائما هوت سبوت حار.
It's okay.
حسنا.
We can have a two-flavored pot.
يمكننا الحصول على وعاء ذو ​​نكهتين.
Right?
حق؟
What sauce do you want?
ما الصلصة التي تريدها؟
- Pepper. - Sesame sauce.
- فلفل.  - صلصة سمسم.
Don't bother.
لا تهتم.
Xiangxiang prefers pepper too.
يفضل Xiangxiang الفلفل أيضًا.
She likes river snails rice noodles.
تحب نودلز الأرز في حلزون النهر.
Stinky tofu.
التوفو النتن.
Durian.
دوريان.
Sausages.
النقانق.
Salty bean curd.
خثارة الفاصوليا المالحة.
Chives, but not coriander.
الثوم المعمر ، ولكن ليس الكزبرة.
Fried chicken with milk tea.
دجاج مقلي مع شاي الحليب.
Large milk tea with full sugar and ice.
شاي حليب كبير مع سكر كامل وثلج.
How come you know so much about me?
كيف لك أن تعرف الكثير عني؟
Your mom told me.
قالت لي والدتك.
Mr. Fu.
السيد فو.
You haven't met her mom, right?
أنت لم تقابل والدتها ، أليس كذلك؟
I'm so full.
اني ممتلئ.
This is the free fruit.
هذه هي الفاكهة المجانية.
Enjoy.
يتمتع.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Ah.
آه.
I can do it myself.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Feed me.
أطعمني.
Ah.
آه.
You are a grown-up.
أنت بالغ.
Can't you do it yourself?
لا يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك بنفسك؟
We always do this at home.
نحن دائما نفعل هذا في المنزل.
Right, Xiangxiang?
حق شيانغشيانغ؟
This is a couple's thing we have.
هذا شيء للزوجين لدينا.
You don't understand.
أنت لا تفهم.
Ah.
آه.
Let me feed you.
دعني أطعمك.
Mr. Fu.
السيد فو.
Xiangxiang, for you.
شيانغشيانغ ، من أجلك.
Xiangxiang, are you okay?
شيانغشيانغ ، هل أنت بخير؟
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Stop!
قف!
You two are killing me!
أنتما الاثنان تقتلانني!
Today is the anniversary of our restaurant.
اليوم هو الذكرى السنوية لمطعمنا.
We give you these headwears for couples.
نقدم لكم هذه القبعات للأزواج.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
For couples? I'll have this one.
للأزواج؟  سآخذ هذا.
Xiangxiang.
شيانغشيانغ.
Send me home.
أرسل لي المنزل.
Can you go home by yourself?
هل يمكنك العودة للمنزل بنفسك؟
I can't.
لا أستطبع.
No.
رقم.
She's going home with me.
هي ذاهبة إلى المنزل معي.
She promised me.
لقد وعدتني.
Fine.
بخير.
Chu He.
تشو هي.
Yes.
نعم.
Prepare the car.
جهز السيارة.
Are you two serious?
هل أنتما جادان؟